(this["webpackJsonplets-play-bingo"]=this["webpackJsonplets-play-bingo"]||[]).push([[0],{14:function(e,i,s){},15:function(e,i,s){},17:function(e,i,s){"use strict";s.r(i);var c=s(1),t=s.n(c),o=s(8),a=s.n(o),r=(s(14),s(5)),l=s(2),n=s(9),d=(s(7),s.p+"static/media/sound.5e8c43f9.wav"),f=s.p+"static/media/mouse-click.3753733f.wav",x=s.p+"static/media/error.ea6f95b9.mp3",u=(s(15),s(0));var _=function(e){return Object(u.jsxs)("div",{children:[" ",13===e.question.id?Object(u.jsx)("div",{className:"bg-blue-200 w-16 h-16 sm:w-32 sm:h-32 lg:w-36 lg:h-36 p-2 rounded shadow-lg",children:Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"flex flex-col justify-center sm:mt-5",children:[e.lock?Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"flex flex-col justify-center items-center",children:[Object(u.jsx)("svg",{className:"animate-bounce w-6 h-6 text-amber-900",fill:"none",viewBox:"0 0 24 24",stroke:"currentColor",children:Object(u.jsx)("path",{d:"M19 14l-7 7m0 0l-7-7m7 7V3"})}),Object(u.jsx)("div",{className:"h-4 w-14 sm:h-8 sm:w-24 px-4 bg-yellow-400 hover:bg-blue-700 text-white rounded flex justify-center items-center",children:Object(u.jsx)("div",{onClick:function(i){i.preventDefault(),e.startGame()},className:"text-xs sm:text-sm cursor-pointer",children:"START"})})]}):Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"flex flex-col justify-center items-center text-xxs sm:text-sm font-bold",children:[Object(u.jsxs)("p",{children:["Correct : ",e.correct," "]}),Object(u.jsxs)("p",{children:["Incorrect : ",e.incorrect]}),Object(u.jsxs)("p",{children:["Bingos : ",e.bingo]})]})," "]})}):Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"p-2 rounded w-16 h-16 sm:w-32 sm:h-32 lg:w-36 lg:h-36 shadow-lg flex flex-col justify-center ".concat(e.question.in_correct?"blur-xs bg-red-300 cursor-not-allowed pointer-events:none":e.question.correct?"blur-xs bg-green-300 cursor-not-allowed pointer-events:none":"bg-white"," ").concat(e.lock?"filter blur-sm cursor-not-allowed pointer-events:none":"filter blur-none pointer-events:cursor"),children:[Object(u.jsx)("div",{className:"h-14 sm:h-16 md:h-20 lg:h-24",children:Object(u.jsx)("p",{className:"text-green-800 font-mono text-xxs sm:text-xs",children:e.question.question})}),Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"flex flex-row justify-center",children:[Object(u.jsx)("div",{onClick:function(i){i.preventDefault(),e.lock||e.question.is_selected||e.onClick(e.index,e.question,!0)},className:"h-3 w-6 sm:w-12 sm:h-6 px-3 text-xs bg-green-500 rounded text-white mr-2 text-xxs sm:text-xs flex justify-center items-center cursor-pointer",children:"True"}),Object(u.jsx)("div",{onClick:function(i){i.preventDefault(),e.lock||e.question.is_selected||e.onClick(e.index,e.question,!1)},className:"h-3 w-6 sm:w-12 sm:h-6 px-3 text-xs bg-red-500 rounded text-white text-xxs sm:text-xs flex justify-center items-center cursor-pointer",children:"False"})]})]})," "]})};var h=function(){var e=Object(c.useState)([]),i=Object(l.a)(e,2),s=i[0],t=i[1],o=Object(c.useState)(!0),a=Object(l.a)(o,2),h=a[0],p=a[1],j=Object(c.useState)(),m=Object(l.a)(j,2),g=m[0],b=m[1],w=Object(c.useState)(0),v=Object(l.a)(w,2),O=v[0],q=v[1],y=Object(c.useState)(0),H=Object(l.a)(y,2),W=H[0],k=H[1],B=Object(c.useState)(0),N=Object(l.a)(B,2),S=N[0],C=N[1],J=Object(c.useState)(!1),M=Object(l.a)(J,2),D=M[0];M[1],Object(c.useEffect)((function(){t(n)}),[]);var I=function(e,i,c){var o=Object(r.a)(s);if(o[e].is_selected=!0,t(o),i.answer===c){new Audio(f).play();var a=Object(r.a)(s);a[e].correct=!i.correct,t(a),function(e){(A(e)||T(e)||X(e)||E(e))&&(C(S+1),new Audio(d).play(),b("animate-pulse"),setTimeout((function(){b("")}),2e3))}(i),q(O+1)}else{new Audio(x).play();var l=Object(r.a)(s);l[e].in_correct=!i.in_correct,t(l),k(W+1)}},A=function(e){return s.filter((function(i){return i.position[0]==e.position[0]})).every((function(e){return e.correct}))},T=function(e){return s.filter((function(i){return i.position[1]==e.position[1]})).every((function(e){return e.correct}))},X=function(e){return s.filter((function(i){return e.is_main_diagonal===i.is_main_diagonal})).every((function(e){return e.correct}))},E=function(e){return s.filter((function(i){return e.is_anti_diagonal===i.is_anti_diagonal})).every((function(e){return e.correct}))};return Object(u.jsx)("div",{className:"bg-gradient-to-r from-yellow-100 to-yellow-300 min-h-screen flex items-center justify-center",children:Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"".concat(g," grid grid-cols-5 sm:grid-cols-5 lg:grid-cols-5 xl:grid-cols-5 gap-1"),children:[s.map((function(e,i){return Object(u.jsx)(_,{question:e,lock:h,bingo:S,correct:O,incorrect:W,all_selected:D,onClick:I,startGame:function(){return p((function(e){return!e}))},index:i},e.id)}))," "]})})};a.a.render(Object(u.jsx)(t.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(u.jsx)(h,{})}),document.getElementById("root"))},7:function(e,i,s){},9:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"id":1,"question":"JSX stands for JavaScript XML","choice1":"<script>","choice2":"<javascript>","choice3":"<js>","choice4":"<scripting>","answer":true,"position":[0,0],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":true,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":2,"question":"Is Undefined a javascript data type ?","choice1":"<script href=\'xxx.js\'>","choice2":"<script name=\'xxx.js\'>","choice3":"<script src=\'xxx.js\'>","choice4":"<script file=\'xxx.js\'>","answer":true,"position":[0,1],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":3,"question":"the result of 3+2+\'7\' = 57","choice1":"msgBox(\'Hello World\');","choice2":"alertBox(\'Hello World\');","choice3":"msg(\'Hello World\');","choice4":"alert(\'Hello World\');","answer":true,"position":[0,2],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":4,"question":"JavaScript was developed by Netscape ?","choice1":"<script>","choice2":"<javascript>","choice3":"<js>","choice4":"<scripting>","answer":true,"position":[0,3],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":5,"question":"var keyword is block scoped","answer":false,"position":[0,4],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":true},{"id":6,"question":"Is Undefined a javascript data type ?","choice1":"msgBox(\'Hello World\');","choice2":"alertBox(\'Hello World\');","choice3":"msg(\'Hello World\');","choice4":"alert(\'Hello World\');","answer":true,"position":[1,0],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":7,"question":"== strictly checks only for equality","choice1":"<script>","choice2":"<javascript>","choice3":"<js>","choice4":"<scripting>","answer":false,"position":[1,1],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":true,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":8,"question":"let keyword is function scoped","choice1":"<script href=\'xxx.js\'>","choice2":"<script name=\'xxx.js\'>","choice3":"<script src=\'xxx.js\'>","choice4":"<script file=\'xxx.js\'>","answer":false,"position":[1,2],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":9,"question":"Is JavaScript case-sensitive?","choice1":"msgBox(\'Hello World\');","choice2":"alertBox(\'Hello World\');","choice3":"msg(\'Hello World\');","choice4":"alert(\'Hello World\');","answer":true,"position":[1,3],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":true},{"id":10,"question":"(2 == \'2\') will return","choice1":"<script>","choice2":"<javascript>","choice3":"<js>","choice4":"<scripting>","answer":true,"position":[1,4],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":11,"question":"the result of 3+2+\'7\' = 12","choice1":"<script href=\'xxx.js\'>","choice2":"<script name=\'xxx.js\'>","choice3":"<script src=\'xxx.js\'>","choice4":"<script file=\'xxx.js\'>","answer":false,"position":[2,0],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":12,"question":"Can you access Cookie using javascript? ","choice1":"msgBox(\'Hello World\');","choice2":"alertBox(\'Hello World\');","choice3":"msg(\'Hello World\');","choice4":"alert(\'Hello World\');","answer":true,"position":[2,1],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":13,"question":"Conf call Bingo","choice1":"<script>","choice2":"<javascript>","choice3":"<js>","choice4":"<scripting>","answer":false,"position":[2,2],"is_selected":true,"in_correct":false,"correct":true,"is_main_diagonal":true,"is_anti_diagonal":true},{"id":14,"question":"var keyword is block scoped","choice1":"<script href=\'xxx.js\'>","choice2":"<script name=\'xxx.js\'>","choice3":"<script src=\'xxx.js\'>","choice4":"<script file=\'xxx.js\'>","answer":false,"position":[2,3],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":15,"question":"Can you access Cookie using javascript?  ","choice1":"msgBox(\'Hello World\');","choice2":"alertBox(\'Hello World\');","choice3":"msg(\'Hello World\');","choice4":"alert(\'Hello World\');","answer":true,"position":[2,4],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":16,"question":"JSX stands for JavaScript XML","choice1":"<script>","choice2":"<javascript>","choice3":"<js>","choice4":"<scripting>","answer":true,"position":[3,0],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":17,"question":"(2 !== \'2\') will return","choice1":"<script href=\'xxx.js\'>","choice2":"<script name=\'xxx.js\'>","choice3":"<script src=\'xxx.js\'>","choice4":"<script file=\'xxx.js\'>","answer":true,"position":[3,1],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":true},{"id":18,"question":"DOM stands for Document Object Method.","choice1":"msgBox(\'Hello World\');","choice2":"alertBox(\'Hello World\');","choice3":"msg(\'Hello World\');","choice4":"alert(\'Hello World\');","answer":false,"position":[3,2],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":19,"question":"JavaScript is the same as Java.","choice1":"<script>","choice2":"<javascript>","choice3":"<js>","choice4":"<scripting>","answer":false,"position":[3,3],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":true,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":20,"question":"Boolean(10 > 9) returns ?","choice1":"<script href=\'xxx.js\'>","choice2":"<script name=\'xxx.js\'>","choice3":"<script src=\'xxx.js\'>","choice4":"<script file=\'xxx.js\'>","answer":true,"position":[3,4],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":21,"question":"JavaScript was developed by Netscape ?","choice1":"msgBox(\'Hello World\');","choice2":"alertBox(\'Hello World\');","choice3":"msg(\'Hello World\');","choice4":"alert(\'Hello World\');","answer":true,"position":[4,0],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":true},{"id":22,"question":"let keyword is function scoped","choice1":"<script>","choice2":"<javascript>","choice3":"<js>","choice4":"<scripting>","answer":false,"position":[4,1],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":23,"question":"(2 === \'2\') will return","choice1":"<script href=\'xxx.js\'>","choice2":"<script name=\'xxx.js\'>","choice3":"<script src=\'xxx.js\'>","choice4":"<script file=\'xxx.js\'>","answer":false,"position":[4,2],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":24,"question":"Break statement exits from the current loop","answer":true,"position":[4,3],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":false,"is_anti_diagonal":false},{"id":25,"question":"var keyword is block scoped","choice1":"msgBox(\'Hello World\');","choice2":"alertBox(\'Hello World\');","choice3":"msg(\'Hello World\');","choice4":"alert(\'Hello World\');","answer":true,"position":[4,4],"is_selected":false,"in_correct":false,"correct":false,"is_main_diagonal":true,"is_anti_diagonal":false}]')}},[[17,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.09351a4b.chunk.js.map